[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Phelps"]}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "What does it mean to any Olympic athlete?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "it", "mean", "to", "any", "Olympic", "athlete", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "Michael Phelps has definitely earned every single one of these 19 medals that he's won thus far.", "answer_tokens": ["Michael", "Phelps", "has", "definitely", "earned", "every", "single", "one", "of", "these", "19", "medals", "that", "he", "'s", "won", "thus", "far", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "Can it be there when he win eight gold medals?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "it", "be", "there", "when", "he", "win", "eight", "gold", "medals", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "No, it can't be there.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "ca", "n't", "be", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "POS", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "We're debating it because of the history of women's swimming.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "debating", "it", "because", "of", "the", "history", "of", "women", "'s", "swimming", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "Would this debate be on front page of newspapers around the world?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "this", "debate", "be", "on", "front", "page", "of", "newspapers", "around", "the", "world", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "NN", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "It may not be so much of a racial thing.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "may", "not", "be", "so", "much", "of", "a", "racial", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "Are we giving her a bad rap, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "we", "giving", "her", "a", "bad", "rap", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "Well, I don't think we are.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "we", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "ORGAN: Would it happened to an American?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Would", "it", "happened", "to", "an", "American", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "I believe it would.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "believe", "it", "would", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1990s"], "LOCATION": ["China"]}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "Is it not right to at least ask a question?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "not", "right", "to", "at", "least", "ask", "a", "question", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "TO", "IN", "JJS", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "Well, China paid a huge price for what they did in the 1990s.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "China", "paid", "a", "huge", "price", "for", "what", "they", "did", "in", "the", "1990s", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China"]}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "Do you think the part of this is because China are beating America, winning more gold medals, but a jealousy maybe?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "the", "part", "of", "this", "is", "because", "China", "are", "beating", "America", ",", "winning", "more", "gold", "medals", ",", "but", "a", "jealousy", "maybe", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "JJR", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "I: Could it be because China has been performing very well.", "answer_tokens": ["I", ":", "Could", "it", "be", "because", "China", "has", "been", "performing", "very", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "Are we seeing a real resurgence now do you think in gymnastics for the American team?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "we", "seeing", "a", "real", "resurgence", "now", "do", "you", "think", "in", "gymnastics", "for", "the", "American", "team", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "ORGAN: What is the nightmare scenario to deal with for you?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "What", "is", "the", "nightmare", "scenario", "to", "deal", "with", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "There isn't really.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "is", "n't", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "And their job will be to intercept?", "question_tokens": ["And", "their", "job", "will", "be", "to", "intercept", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "There's a range of capabilities we can put in the back of this aircraft.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "a", "range", "of", "capabilities", "we", "can", "put", "in", "the", "back", "of", "this", "aircraft", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "These helicopters could be the fastest rapid response tool that you have on this boat, right?", "question_tokens": ["These", "helicopters", "could", "be", "the", "fastest", "rapid", "response", "tool", "that", "you", "have", "on", "this", "boat", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "That's correct.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "correct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "And they can take off how fast?", "question_tokens": ["And", "they", "can", "take", "off", "how", "fast", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "In a matter of moments.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "a", "matter", "of", "moments", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "This extraordinary looking beast here, what is it?", "question_tokens": ["This", "extraordinary", "looking", "beast", "here", ",", "what", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "This is the OCBP.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "the", "OCBP", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "If there was a major incident down at the Olympics, you could get here pretty quickly from here, right?", "question_tokens": ["If", "there", "was", "a", "major", "incident", "down", "at", "the", "Olympics", ",", "you", "could", "get", "here", "pretty", "quickly", "from", "here", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "You guys are basically armed to the teeth and ready if you need to be, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "guys", "are", "basically", "armed", "to", "the", "teeth", "and", "ready", "if", "you", "need", "to", "be", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": ".", "answer_tokens": ["."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Navy"]}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "POS", "JJS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "What's the difference in terms of what you do as the captain?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "difference", "in", "terms", "of", "what", "you", "do", "as", "the", "captain", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "HMS Ocean is the royal Navy's largest ship.", "answer_tokens": ["HMS", "Ocean", "is", "the", "royal", "Navy", "'s", "largest", "ship", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "And would you say from all your experience that we're ready?", "question_tokens": ["And", "would", "you", "say", "from", "all", "your", "experience", "that", "we", "'re", "ready", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "Very much so.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "much", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "I mean how much food are you serving a day for these guys?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "how", "much", "food", "are", "you", "serving", "a", "day", "for", "these", "guys", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "At the moment we've got just over a thousand people on board.", "answer_tokens": ["At", "the", "moment", "we", "'ve", "got", "just", "over", "a", "thousand", "people", "on", "board", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "Is it as terrifying to do it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "as", "terrifying", "to", "do", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "Well, you know, I've often said that anyone who's done bobsleigh, especially as a driver, if they weren't scared once during their career, they weren't real bobsledders.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "'ve", "often", "said", "that", "anyone", "who", "'s", "done", "bobsleigh", ",", "especially", "as", "a", "driver", ",", "if", "they", "were", "n't", "scared", "once", "during", "their", "career", ",", "they", "were", "n't", "real", "bobsledders", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "How many -- there are six I heard?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "--", "there", "are", "six", "I", "heard", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", ":", "EX", "VBP", "CD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "We have six athletes.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "have", "six", "athletes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["South Africa"]}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "What would you feel about South Africa today?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "feel", "about", "South", "Africa", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "I'm always optimistic about South Africa.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "always", "optimistic", "about", "South", "Africa", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["South Africa"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["United Nations"]}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "What do you think of him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "Yes, I met him at the United Nations a couple of years ago.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "met", "him", "at", "the", "United", "Nations", "a", "couple", "of", "years", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "America"]}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "Well, I think America -- we still look up to America in many ways.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "America", "--", "we", "still", "look", "up", "to", "America", "in", "many", "ways", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "Does that go for your children too?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "go", "for", "your", "children", "too", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "I don't know about that as yet.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "about", "that", "as", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "What do you think she would have made of the way that you have conducted yourself since you had to take over the reins of the palace?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "she", "would", "have", "made", "of", "the", "way", "that", "you", "have", "conducted", "yourself", "since", "you", "had", "to", "take", "over", "the", "reins", "of", "the", "palace", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "First of all, I can't believe it's already 30 years since her passing.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "I", "ca", "n't", "believe", "it", "'s", "already", "30", "years", "since", "her", "passing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "But for those who didn't know your mother, how would you describe her?", "question_tokens": ["But", "for", "those", "who", "did", "n't", "know", "your", "mother", ",", "how", "would", "you", "describe", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "She was the most warm, gracious, engaging person.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "was", "the", "most", "warm", ",", "gracious", ",", "engaging", "person", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "Do you have any American citizenship because of your mother?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "American", "citizenship", "because", "of", "your", "mother", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "I never actually had a passport, but I had a paper in my passport that said when I was to travel to the United States, I shouldn't be considered as a foreign citizen.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "never", "actually", "had", "a", "passport", ",", "but", "I", "had", "a", "paper", "in", "my", "passport", "that", "said", "when", "I", "was", "to", "travel", "to", "the", "United", "States", ",", "I", "should", "n't", "be", "considered", "as", "a", "foreign", "citizen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", ",", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "How's it going, Princess Charlene?", "question_tokens": ["How", "'s", "it", "going", ",", "Princess", "Charlene", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "Very well, thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "well", ",", "thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "Life is good as Princess Charlene?", "question_tokens": ["Life", "is", "good", "as", "Princess", "Charlene", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "Busy.", "answer_tokens": ["Busy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "What is the reality of entering a royal family?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "reality", "of", "entering", "a", "royal", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "Well, from what I've experienced, it's very busy, a lot of responsibilities.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "from", "what", "I", "'ve", "experienced", ",", "it", "'s", "very", "busy", ",", "a", "lot", "of", "responsibilities", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "Other than being married to this charming, handsome prince?", "question_tokens": ["Other", "than", "being", "married", "to", "this", "charming", ",", "handsome", "prince", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "I get to wear a tiara now and then.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "get", "to", "wear", "a", "tiara", "now", "and", "then", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "did you ever think, one day I want to be a princess, marry a handsome prince?", "question_tokens": ["did", "you", "ever", "think", ",", "one", "day", "I", "want", "to", "be", "a", "princess", ",", "marry", "a", "handsome", "prince", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "I wanted to be Zoro.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "wanted", "to", "be", "Zoro", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Well, it's not true, is it?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "true", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "There is an upside.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "is", "an", "upside", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["South Africa"]}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "NNS", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "Why is that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "RINCESS CHARLENE: Well, training in South Africa, I was, you know often training alongside athletes that had disabilities and, you know, they also tried to get to their meets, to reach their goals in life, very little support.", "answer_tokens": ["RINCESS", "CHARLENE", ":", "Well", ",", "training", "in", "South", "Africa", ",", "I", "was", ",", "you", "know", "often", "training", "alongside", "athletes", "that", "had", "disabilities", "and", ",", "you", "know", ",", "they", "also", "tried", "to", "get", "to", "their", "meets", ",", "to", "reach", "their", "goals", "in", "life", ",", "very", "little", "support", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "How do you view it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "view", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "Well, I wouldn't say expensive or inexpensive.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "n't", "say", "expensive", "or", "inexpensive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "As one of the main sponsors, how do you feel about what NBC is doing, which is basically ignoring the rally cry to be airing the big events live and they're sticking to their prime-time schedule?", "question_tokens": ["As", "one", "of", "the", "main", "sponsors", ",", "how", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "what", "NBC", "is", "doing", ",", "which", "is", "basically", "ignoring", "the", "rally", "cry", "to", "be", "airing", "the", "big", "events", "live", "and", "they", "'re", "sticking", "to", "their", "prime-time", "schedule", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "Piers, it's a great question.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "great", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NBC"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "What do you think about the -- people like I guess Starbucks for example opening factories back in America at a bit of a loss leader, but doing it to make a point, we want to bring jobs back to America?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "about", "the", "--", "people", "like", "I", "guess", "Starbucks", "for", "example", "opening", "factories", "back", "in", "America", "at", "a", "bit", "of", "a", "loss", "leader", ",", "but", "doing", "it", "to", "make", "a", "point", ",", "we", "want", "to", "bring", "jobs", "back", "to", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ":", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "You know, Piers, I don't think there's a very simple answer for all of that.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "there", "'s", "a", "very", "simple", "answer", "for", "all", "of", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Starbucks"], "LOCATION": ["America", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "Whoever wins in November, what should they do about that?", "question_tokens": ["Whoever", "wins", "in", "November", ",", "what", "should", "they", "do", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "They ought to take a look at -- they ought to understand, business is not the enemy.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "ought", "to", "take", "a", "look", "at", "--", "they", "ought", "to", "understand", ",", "business", "is", "not", "the", "enemy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "If they made it more attractive for businesses like yours to bring factories back to America, would you do that?", "question_tokens": ["If", "they", "made", "it", "more", "attractive", "for", "businesses", "like", "yours", "to", "bring", "factories", "back", "to", "America", ",", "would", "you", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "TO", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "I would have to say we would consider it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "have", "to", "say", "we", "would", "consider", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", ",", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 637, "question": "You've been quicker in your career, haven't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "been", "quicker", "in", "your", "career", ",", "have", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "Not running, that's why I row.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "running", ",", "that", "'s", "why", "I", "row", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 641, "question": "Was it receiving it from the great Becks?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "receiving", "it", "from", "the", "great", "Becks", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 642, "answer": "I think it probably was being asked to do it in the first place.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "probably", "was", "being", "asked", "to", "do", "it", "in", "the", "first", "place", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "VBG", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 651, "question": "What is it about the Olympics that makes great champions keep coming back, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "about", "the", "Olympics", "that", "makes", "great", "champions", "keep", "coming", "back", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", "VB", "VBG", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "It is the biggest sporting event there is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "the", "biggest", "sporting", "event", "there", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mark Spitz"]}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "JJ", ",", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 659, "question": "Who is your favorite Olympian in the world, ever?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "is", "your", "favorite", "Olympian", "in", "the", "world", ",", "ever", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 660, "answer": "I think, going back, it would probably be when I was a 10- year-old, of watching Mark Spitz win his seventh.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", ",", "going", "back", ",", "it", "would", "probably", "be", "when", "I", "was", "a", "10-", "year-old", ",", "of", "watching", "Mark", "Spitz", "win", "his", "seventh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 668, "question": "Do you think people have any real understanding of the sacrifice and the dedication that it takes to be the best when you come to the Olympics?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "people", "have", "any", "real", "understanding", "of", "the", "sacrifice", "and", "the", "dedication", "that", "it", "takes", "to", "be", "the", "best", "when", "you", "come", "to", "the", "Olympics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 669, "answer": "I think most people do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "most", "people", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "If I case say you could have only one of those, which would you take?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "case", "say", "you", "could", "have", "only", "one", "of", "those", ",", "which", "would", "you", "take", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "CD", "IN", "DT", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "It would have to be the medals.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "would", "have", "to", "be", "the", "medals", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 690, "question": "Do you still row?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "row", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 691, "answer": "I've been out in a boat five times this year.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "been", "out", "in", "a", "boat", "five", "times", "this", "year", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]